Alright folks, in this series we are drawing magical objects and in this clip I'm going to teach you how to draw a magic lamp.
I'm going to do that right down here.
So obviously you know the story roughly behind the magic lamp.
Everyone is sort of familiar with the little genie thing.
What we are going to do is we are going to start by drawing the rough shape and I would say the rough shape of a lamp, a magic lamp is almost like the head of an elephant.
It has got a little head and then what we'll do you might equate to a long snout, trunk.
So we'll come in here and we'll draw the tip of the lamp first and that is obviously where the magic happens right there.
Then we'll come up here and we'll draw the top, the little lid where they have, obviously pour in the oil and things like that.
And then we come in here and we'll draw the handle something like this right there.
Then the base which would be something like this that it has got to be able to stand on.
Come on down just like that and then obviously we will add some details to it just to make it look more interesting, just like that and then you know if you want to you can add a polished sort of shine to it if you want and texture it a bit just to make it look a bit more interesting but that is basically it.
The genie's magic lamp.